hoaxorfact.com 2018-02-22

# Privacy Policy - Hoax Or Fact

  * We use technologies like cookies (small files stored on your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address.
  * We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. With your permission, we may also access other personal information on your device, such as your phone book, calendar or messages, in order to provide services to you. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook.
  * Our systems may associate this personal information with your activities in the course of providing service to you (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for).
  * We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.
  * To customize our service for you, we may collect and store your precise geographic location as part of your user profile. This data generally is not shared with others. We may ask for your consent on your first use of the service.
  * You can sign into your account to see or delete any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, address, email or phone number. You can also contact us by email to request to see or delete this information.
  * We remove personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email or phone number) and other preferences associated with your account promptly after you delete your account. We may retain other data indefinitely.
  * We may share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with trusted partners in order to provide you with relevant advertising, offers or services.
  * California residents are legally entitled (at no charge and no more than once annually) to request information about how we may have shared your information with others for direct marketing purposes. Contact us for this information:Contact US OR eMail us at siddhartha[at]hoaxorfact.com
  * Ad companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customize content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. Interest and location data may be linked to your device, but is not linked to your identity. Click to see company privacy policies and opt-out choices:
  * Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data.

  * We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.
  * Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.
  * To operate the service, we also may make identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so.
  * This privacy policy was last updated on 19 March 2013. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text.

  * If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us OR send eMail siddhartha[at]hoaxorfact.com

### You may also like

  * [

](http://www.hoaxorfact.com/technology/reliance-jio-launched-jiocoin-app-cryptocurrency.html "Reliance Jio Launched JioCoin and App of Cryptocurrency: Fact Check")

__161 __76

  * [

](http://www.hoaxorfact.com/celebrities/sylvester-stallone-dies-battling-cancer.html "Sylvester Stallone Dies Battling Cancer: Fact Check")

__217 __60

  * [

](http://www.hoaxorfact.com/crime/dog-meat-sale-allowed-los-angeles-restaurant-fact-check.html "Dog Meat Sale Allowed in Los Angeles Restaurant: Fact Check")

__237 __68
